ABOUT ME

I am a combat Veteran turned Dev Nerd.

Projects

2019 Revirr.com - Revirr is here to help with the process by offering true entry level professional positions as well as a guide to show what you may qualify for based on degree, experience, skills and interests.

Powered by: Wordpress

2019 ChalkingCode.com - Learn how to code from front end to backend.

Powered by: Github

CONTACT



978 Radcliffe Rd



Towson, Md 301-996-4681



skylarbarrow man@gmail.com

INTERESTS

Coding

My Dog

Binge watching Netflix

Sports

Coffee

Skylar Barrowman

WEB DEVELOPER

CAREER OBJECTIVE

To be able to work for an encouraging company that will assist me in developing, improving, and obtaining the necessary skills in order to become the best engineer possible.

EDUCATION

FreeCodeCamp

Full Stack Development

The Odin Project

Front End development

W3C Schools

Front and back end dev

TECHNICAL PROFICIENCIES:

JavaScript, JQuery, HTML, HTML5, CSS, CSS3, Web Programming Skills, E-Commerce, Teamwork, Verbal Communication, cross-browser compatibility, Web User Interface Design (UI), Security Principles, Object-Oriented Design, Web Services (REST/SOAP), Multimedia Content Development, API's

EXPERIENCE

Platform Ops/Platform Specialist

2017 to present | Zerofox

– Baltimore, Md

 $\label{thm:contributor} Key contributor to startup company's fast evolution from manually doing work to automating the small things.$

- Created and maintained Foxscripts (Java) to appropriately identify harmful social media content.
- Spearheaded and published research regarding security on social media networks. Mentioned by Wired, Huffington Post, CNN and many other popular sources.
- $\bullet \text{Award the Unsung Hero Award for significant transformative contributions in support of Zerofox's mission. } \\$
- Automated the health check system by utilizing API's increasing efficiency by 75%
- Analyzed the inefficiencies and pain points of current workflow and built a series of python scripts.

MILITARY EXPERIENCE

USMC Infantry Team Leader

2011–2015 Operation enduring Freedom 2013 Afghanistan

Army Reserves

2015–2017 343rd medical co ground ambulance

2017-Present 450th Civil affairs batt (airborne)

EXPERTISE

CMS Customizations and plugin development Widget development

Gimp/Photoshop

Framework knowledge



Global Project Management ••••

SKILLS

Attentive listening and effective oral communication skills

Great at Problem Solving

Good Leadership Skills

Critical Thinker

Ability to quickly create and apply ideas and solutions

